What's up, y'all?
Now, remember I told you I was gonna be interviewing
Shakira Autry.
Now, Shakira is the Buffalo Blizzard hero.
Remember, the old man had fell in the snow
and she went outside and brought him in her house
and she nursed him and got him safe
and got him to the hospital.
Yes!
I cried about it.
I shared it with y'all.
Well, she's gonna be on Small Doses Podcast this week
and I will be premiering it Thursday at 4 p.m. Pacific
and I'm gonna be in the chat.
So, I will see you there at YouTube, Amanda Seals TV,
talking about what's going on on the podcast
as it is happening right there live
in front of y'all face.
Such your reminder.
Such you don't miss it.
It's gonna be a good one.
Side Effects of Being a Good Samaritan
with Shakira Rain Autry.
Premiering Thursday at 4 p.m. Pacific
on YouTube, Amanda Seals TV.